A Guide to the Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund for Music records FA1420
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Project Files, 1955-1983; 1; 58.87 Cubic Feet 155 letter-size document boxes. Boxes 1-155.
  - M-N-O-P-Q
    - Mandel, Janet (Box 76, Folder 27)
    - Manes, Stephen (Box 76, Folder 28)
    - Manhasset Bay Opera Association (Box 76, Folder 29)
    - Manhattan Consort (Box 76, Folder 30)
    - Manhattan School of Music, 1967-1971 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Manhattan School of Music, 1962-1966 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Manhattan Singers (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Manhattan Theatre Club, Inc. (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Maniates, M. Rika (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Mann, Jerome (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Mann, Laura (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Mannes College of Music (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Mannheimer, Frank (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Mannion, Elizabeth (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Mannis, Sandra (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Manno, Robert (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Manoogian, Vartan (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Mansouri, Lotfollah (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Maravell, Peter (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Marchand, Andreas (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Marco, John (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Marconi, Valentino (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Marcoux, Janice (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Marcus, Genevieve (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Marek, Dan (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Maresca, Rosalia (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Margolis, Sanford (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Mark, Peter (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Markevitch, Dimitry (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Marks, Virginia (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Marlboro Music, 1968-1982 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Marlboro School of Music, 1957-1967 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Marlotti, Vincent (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Markmiller, Inge (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Marquart, Stephen (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Marra, Aldo (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Marsee, Susan (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - Marsh, Calvin (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Marsh, Jane (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Marsh, Marian (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Marshall, Donald (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Marshall, Elizabeth (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Marshall, Jean (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Marshall, John - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Marshall, Kay (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Marshall, Richard (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Marshall, Robert (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Martin, Charlotte (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Martin, David (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Martin, Dennis (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Martin, Frances (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Martin, Janis (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Martin, Thomas (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Martin, Wendy (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Martinez, Artless (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - Marvin, Marajean (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - Marvin, Robert (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Mary, Carolann (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - Maschat, Erik (Box 79, Folder 22)
    - Mason, Ethel Mae (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - Mason, Harold Edward (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - Masselos, William (Box 79, Folder 25)
    - Massenkoff, Nicolai (Box 79, Folder 26)
    - Master Institute of United Arts (Box 79, Folder 27)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology Choral Society (Box 79, Folder 28)
    - Masterworks Chorus Music and Art Festival (Box 79, Folder 29)
    - Masterworks Theatre, Inc. (Box 79, Folder 30)
    - Mastrangelo, Maria (Box 79, Folder 31)
    - Mastrangelo, Paul (Box 79, Folder 32)
    - Mate, Peter Janos (Box 79, Folder 33)
    - Mateo, Felix (Box 79, Folder 34)
    - Matesky, Elizabeth (Box 79, Folder 35)
    - Mathis, James (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Mathis, Joyce (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Matsumoto, Miss Shigemi (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Matsuo, Yoko (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Matteo, Alessandra (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Matthes, Carl (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Matthews, Benjamin F. (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Matthews, Clifton (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Matthews, Justus (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Matthias, Miltiades A. (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Matushevski, Voytek (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Mauborgne, Helen (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Mauk, Frederick (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Maurice, Glenda (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Mauro-Tscheresky, Luba (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Mavrikos, Lambryn (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Maxwell, Ms. Linn (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Maxwell, Rosalie (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - Maxymuk, Nicholas (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - May, Ernest (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - Mayer, James (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - May, Frederick David (Box 80, Folder 22)
    - Mayes, Doris (Box 80, Folder 23)
    - Mays, Walter A. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Mazzarella, Robert (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Mazzolini, Joseph (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - McAlister, Barbara (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - McCallick, Charles (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - McCann, Delores (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - McCarty, Patty Sue (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - McCaughna, Daniel (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - McCauley, Barry (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - McCelland, Louise (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - McClung, Marjorie (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - McCollum, John (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - McCollum, Sadie (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - McCoy, Seth (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - McCracken, James E. (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - McCray, James (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - McCray, Mack (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - McCullough, Oscar (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - McDaniel, Frances (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - McDevitt, Kerry (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - McDonald, James (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - McDonald, Joyce (Box 81, Folder 22)
    - McDonald, Susann (Box 81, Folder 23)
    - McDonald, William (Box 81, Folder 24)
    - McFarlane, Ralph (Box 81, Folder 25)
    - McGarrity, Evelyn (Box 81, Folder 26)
    - McGaugh, Shirley (Box 81, Folder 27)
    - McGee, Patricia Ann (Box 81, Folder 28)
    - McGifford, Michael (Box 81, Folder 29)
    - McGill, Frank (Box 81, Folder 30)
    - McGrath, William (Box 81, Folder 31)
    - McGrew, Patricia (Box 81, Folder 32)
    - McGuffee, Virgie (Box 81, Folder 33)
    - McGuire, Edward (Box 81, Folder 34)
    - Mc Intosh, Thomas (Box 81, Folder 35)
    - McIntyre, Joy (Box 81, Folder 36)
    - Mckee. Richard (Box 81, Folder 37)
    - McKinney, William (Box 81, Folder 38)
    - McKissic, James (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - McKnight, Emily (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - McLane, Armand (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - McLane, Greer (Ms.) (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - McLean, John (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - McMechen, June (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - McMurray, Mary (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - McWhorter. George (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Mead, Ernest C. (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Meadow, Leslie (Mr.) (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Megremis, Yeoryia (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Meier, Johanna (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Meinzer-Wright, Jacqueline (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Melachouris, Molly (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - Melchior, Lauritz (Box 82, Folder 15)
    - Melin, William (Box 82, Folder 16)
    - Memphis Opera Theatre (Box 82, Folder 17)
    - Mendelson, Jacob (Box 82, Folder 18)
    - Yehudi Menuhin Music Foundation, Inc. (Box 82, Folder 19)
    - Merian, Alan (Box 82, Folder 20)
    - Meriweather, Annette (Box 82, Folder 21)
    - Mernick, Lillian (Box 82, Folder 22)
    - Merrill, Patti (Box 82, Folder 23)
    - Merritt, Helen (Box 82, Folder 24)
    - Messina, Lillian (Box 82, Folder 25)
    - Mesta, Michael (Box 82, Folder 26)
    - Metcalf, William (Box 82, Folder 27)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Young Artist Series, 1962-1967 (Box 82, Folder 28)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Young Artist Series, 1956-1963 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art - All Series, 1956-1963 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Bach Series (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Chamber Orchestra Series (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Sonata Series (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Metropolitan National Company (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Metropolitan Opera Association (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Metropolitan Opera Guild (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Metropolitan Sinfonietta Society (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Meyer, Janet (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Meyer, Joyce (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Meyers, H. Emerson (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Michaels, Astrid (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Michaels, Geoffrey (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Michalaros, Aliki (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Michalski, Raymond (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - Milbourne, Omega (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - Michell, Edna (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - Michigan State University, 1970-1979 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Michigan State University (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Miculs, Melita (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Mid-America Chorale (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Middaugh, Benjamin (Box 84, Folder 4A)
    - Middleton, Jaynne (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Migenes, Julia (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Milan, Linda (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Miles, John (tenor) (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Miles, Jonathan (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Milito, Quinto (Mr.) (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Milius, Richard (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Milkie, Paul (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Millburn, Ellsworth (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Miller, Barbara (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Miller, Deborah (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Miller, Donald (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Miller, Douglas Barton (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Miller, Janet Desiree (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Miller, John (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Miller, Kathy (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Miller, Laurel (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Miller, Philip (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Miller, Ms. Robin (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Miller, Ronald (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Miller, William (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Milligan, Thomas B. (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Millner, Frederick (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Milnes, Sherrill (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Miner, Erica (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Minnesota Opera Company, 1966-1972 (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - Minnesota Opera Company, 1966-1969 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Minnesota Orchestra (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Minocci, Theresa (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Miramar Center for the Performing Arts (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Misslin, Patricia (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Mitchell, Lawrence (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Mittleman, Norman (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Miville, Rene (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Mizrahi, Morris (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Mobile Theatre Guild (Alabama) (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Modenos, John (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Molteni, Dolores (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Monahan, Kathleen (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Monath, Hortense (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Monath, Hortense (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Monette, LaVergne (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - Monk, Dennis (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Monosoff, Sonya (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Monson, Craig (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Montagnana New Music Foundation (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Montagu, David (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Montal, Andre (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Montalvo, Flavia (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Montana Arts Center (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Montane, Carlos (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Montclaire Art Museum, Monteclaire, NY (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Montecino, Alfonso (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Montefiore, David (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Montes, Orlando (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Monteux (Pierre) Memorial Fund (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Montgomery, David (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Montoya, Betty (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Moody-Morris, Janet (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - Mooney, Thomas (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - Moore, David W. (Box 87, Folder 19)
    - Moore, Dr. Douglas (Box 87, Folder 20)
    - Moore, Ms. Marion (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Moore, Ruth (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Moore, Sharon (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Morales, Abe (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Morcom-Kelm, Joan (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Mordino, Joseph (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - More, Michael (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - More, Michael (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Moretti, Diane (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Morey, Carl R. (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Morgan, Mac (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Morgan, Margery (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Morganstern, Daniel (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Morrill, Theodore (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Morris, Emma Jefferson (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - Morris, James (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Morris, Martha (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - Morris, Ruth (Box 88, Folder 18)
    - Morrow, Ruth (Box 88, Folder 19)
    - Morse, Carol (Box 88, Folder 20)
    - Morvaya, Leonore (Box 88, Folder 21)
    - Moser, Thomas (Box 88, Folder 22)
    - Mosher, Elizabeth (Box 88, Folder 23)
    - Mosley, Robert (Box 88, Folder 24)
    - Mott, Kathleen (Box 88, Folder 25)
    - Moulson, Robert (Box 88, Folder 26)
    - The Mount Desert Festival of Chamber Music (Box 88, Folder 27)
    - Mount, John (Box 88, Folder 28)
    - Mower-Garner, Linne (Mrs.) (Box 88, Folder 29)
    - Moynagh, Joan (Box 88, Folder 30)
    - Mozart Festival Orchestra (Box 88, Folder 31)
    - Mueller, Carol Ann (Box 88, Folder 32)
    - Muhlbauer, Gilda (Box 88, Folder 33)
    - Muller, Edward (Box 88, Folder 34)
    - Mulreed, James (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Mulvey, Marilyn (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Mumper, Robert (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Mundt, Richard (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Munguia, Gilberto (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Municpal Concerts, Inc. (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Munson, Ronald (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Murphy, Christine (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Murphy, Donna (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Murphy, Joseph (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Murray, Jack (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Murray, Jane (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Murray, Matthew (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - Murray, Sterling (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Murray, William (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Museum Circuit for Young Artists (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Museum Concerts, Inc. (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - Museum of Modern Art - Stein (Box 89, Folder 20)
    - Museum Project (Box 89, Folder 21)
    - Music Academy of the West (Box 89, Folder 22)
    - Music Associates of Aspen, 1967-1979 (Box 89, Folder 23)
    - Music Associates of Aspen, 1955-1966 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Music Committee of the People to People Program of the United States (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Music Education League (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Music House Concerts (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Music in Our Time, 1967-1974 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Music in Our Time, 1959-1966 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Music in the Making (Cooper Union), 1958-1968 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Music Library Association, 1959-1974 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Music of the Baroque (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Music Performance Trust Fund (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Music Production and Sales Consultants,Ltd. (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Music Research Foundation (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Music Teachers National Association (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Musical America (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Musical Arts Research Development Institute (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Musicians Club of America (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Musicians' Foundation, Inc. (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Musicology Program, 1978-1979 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Musicology Program, 1977-1978 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Musicology, 1976-1977 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Musicology, 1975-1976 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Musicology, 1974-1975 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Musicology, 1973-1974 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Musicology, 1972-1973 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Musicology, 1971-1972 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Musicology, 1970-1971 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Musicology, 1969-1970 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Musicology, 1968-1969 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Musicology, 1967-1968 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Musicology, 1966-1967 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Musicology, 1965-1966 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Musicology, 1964-1965 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Musicology, 1963-1964 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Musicology, 1960-1962 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Musicology - Chapters, Drafts, Committee (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Musicology - General Study (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Musicology - Survey, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Mutual of Omaha (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Myers, John Wesley (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Myers, Patricia (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Myers, Suzanne (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Myrvold, David (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Nabore, William (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Nadeau, Lise (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Nadler, Sheila (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Naldi, Ronald (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Nall, Nan (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Napper, Charles M. - Pro Musia Limited (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Nash, Elizabeth H. (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Nashville Symphony Orchestra (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Natale, Louise (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Nathanson, Carol (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - National Association of Concert Managers (Lombard) (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - National Association of Schools of Music (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - National Association of Teachers of Singing (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - National Choral Council (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - National Council of Women - Music Committee (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - National Cultural Center (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - National Educational TV (NET) (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - National Federation of Music Clubs (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - National Guild of Community Music Schools (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - National Music Camp (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - National Music League - Financial Information (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - National Music League - Action Papers (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - National Opera Institute, 1970-1979 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - National Research Center for the Arts (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Neal, Joanne (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Neal, John (Box 95, Folder 6A)
    - Neikrug, Barry (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Neikrug, George (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Neill, William (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - National Orchestral Association (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Neiman, Lea (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Nelson, Alice Marie (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Nelson, Gail Evangelyn (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Nelson, Howard (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Nelson, Jane (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Nelson, Karla (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Nelson, Marigay (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Nelson, Wendell (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Netherlands Chamber Ensemble (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Netherlands Empresariaat (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Nettles, Marian (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Neugeboren, Barbara (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Neuhaus, Max (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Neuman, Maxine (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Neumann, Alfred J. (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Nevison, Howard (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - New Amsterdam Ensemble (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Newark Art Museum, Newark, NJ (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - New Boston Percussion Emsemble (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - Neway, Patricia (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - New Britain Symphony Society (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - New Chamber Players (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - Newcomb, Anthony (Box 96, Folder 24)
    - New Dimenstions in Music (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - New England Conservatory (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - New England Contemporary Ensemble (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - New England Opera Theatre - Action Papers (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - New England Opera Theatre - General Correspondence (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - New England Regional Opera Company (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - New England Woodwind Quintet (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - New Hamphire Music Festival (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - New Haven Chorale (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - New Haven Opera Society, Inc. (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Newhouse, Ruth (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - New Jersey Symphony Orchestra (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Newman, Donna (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Newman, Linda (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - New Music Circle (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - New Music Ensemble (Rhode Island) (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - New Orleans Friends of Music (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - New School of Music (Philadelphia) (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Newton, Norma (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - New School of Music (Philadelphia) (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - New World Consort (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - New World Trio (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - New York Associates for the Blind (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - New York Brass Quintet (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - New York Brass Society (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - New York Chamber Ensemble (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - New York Chamber Soloists (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - New York Chamber Symphony (A. Lief) (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - New York Choral Society (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - New York City Opera (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - New York City Opera Studio (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - New York Lyric Arts Trio (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - New York Orchestral Society (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - New York Philharmonic (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - New York Philomusica - Chamber Ensemble (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - New York Pro Musica Antiqua - Motet Choir (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - New York Pro Musica Antiqua (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - New York Pro Musica Antiqua - Dockets, Payments, Letters (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - New York State Opera League (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Nichols, Clinton (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Nicholson, Errol Anthony (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Nickel, Matilda (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Nicks, Nancy (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Nicholescu, Valeria (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Nielsen, Nicolai (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Nielsen, Dawn (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Nieman, Henry (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Ninomiya, Linda (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Nisstad, David (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Nix, William (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Nocera, Rosine (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - Nodova, Ms. Faina (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - Noel, Carol (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - Noel, Rita (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - Nolen, Timothy (Box 100, Folder 20)
    - Nolte, Edgar (Box 100, Folder 21)
    - Norell, Judith (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Norman, Jessye (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Norris, Martha H. (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Nors, Stan (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - North Carolina School of the Arts (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - North Carolina Symphony Society (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Northfield Schools (MA) (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - North Shore Opera Company (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Norton, Jocelyn (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Norton, Maureen (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Norwood, Jacqueline (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Novak, Maria (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Novich, Mija (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - Nower, Floyd (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - Nowicki, Barbara Ann (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - Nowicki, I. Frank (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - Nugent, George (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - Nunez, Ivan (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - Nuss, William (Box 101, Folder 19)
    - Oakland Symphony (Box 101, Folder 20)
    - Oberjat, Thomas (Box 101, Folder 21)
    - Oberlin Music Theater (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - O'Brien, James V. (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Ocasio, Benjamin (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - O'Connor, Thomas (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - O'Doan, Neal D. (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Oelbaum, Michael (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Ogg, Janette (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Oglebay Institute, 1958-1964 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Oglebay Institute, 1965-1973 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Ohio University (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Ohm, Karen (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Ojai Festival, 1971-1982 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Ohlson, Miss Gunnel (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - Oldham, Denver (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - O'Leary, Thomas (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - Olefsky, Paul (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - Oliphint, Bernadine (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - Oliver, Irene (Box 102, Folder 18)
    - Olvis, William (Box 102, Folder 19)
    - Omvig, Janice Fleming (Box 102, Folder 20)
    - O'Neill, Charles (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - O'Neill, Jack (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - O'Neill, Patricia (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Opera Company of Boston, Inc., 1966-1978 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Opera Guild of Greater Miami (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Opera New England, Inc., 1974-1977 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Opera Society of Washington (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Opera Theatre of St. Louis, 1964-1975 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Opera Today (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Opportunity Resources for the Arts (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Orantes, Teresa (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - The Orchestra of America (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Orchestra U.S.A. (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Orchestral Camera Treatment (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Orchestral Society of American Artists (Box 104, Folder 9)